I thought I had it all together
But I was led astray The day you walked away
You were the clock that was ticking in my heart
Changed my state of mind When love's so hard to find
Your feelings changed like the weather
Went from clear to gray
On that cloudy day
How can I go on Without falling apart
Love's so hard to find When someone's on your mind
Listen baby
Your wish is my command
Baby won't you understand
That your wish is my command
What can I do to make my baby understand
Something tells me that I'm dreaming
I can see us there Waving unaware
Of problems that have a tendency to keep
Keep the truth confined Far from our minds
You need someone you can believe in
This I do declare Trust me I'll be there
The road that leads to heaven can be so steep
I will help you climb Change your state of mind
Listen baby
Your wish is my command
Baby won't you understand
That your wish is my command
What can I do to make my baby understand
Your wish is my command
Baby won't you understand
That your wish is my command
I can see us there Waving unaware
This I do declare Trust me I'll be there
Listen baby
Your wish is my command
Baby won't you understand
That your wish is my command
What can I do to make my baby understand
Follow me into, into my sleep
Baby I'm yours, I'm yours to keep
You've got the magic That entered my heart and my mind
Your wish is my command
Baby won't you understand Your wish is my command
Baby won't you understand
Your wish is my command
Good job!